http://www.savebritainsheritage.org/support-us/privacy-policy

Support Us
Why donate? Become a Friend Become a Saviour SAVE Patrons Legacies Fighting Fund Volunteer Thank you Privacy Policy Online Payment
About the Register
Search the Register How to save a Building at Risk BaR News Useful Contacts
Publications
Publications
Publications in Print e-Reports Publications Out of Print SAVE Europe Publications
Help & Advice
Introduction
Forming an action group The Campaign Use of the media Local Planners and Planning Applications Getting a building spotlisted Conservation area designation Establishing a trust Stopping the rot Legal Action Sources of further help and advice Links
SAVE Europe
Introduction
Manifesto Trustees Europe News Accounts
Home
About Us
Support Us
Campaigns
Events
Support Us
Why donate? Become a Friend Become a Saviour SAVE Patrons Legacies Fighting Fund Volunteer Thank you Privacy Policy Online Payment
Current Campaigns
Past Campaigns Announcements Newsletters Recent Publicity
Upcoming Events
Past Events
About the Register
Search the Register How to save a Building at Risk BaR News Useful Contacts
Publications
Publications in Print e-Reports Publications Out of Print SAVE Europe Publications
Introduction
Forming an action group The Campaign Use of the media Local Planners and Planning Applications Getting a building spotlisted Conservation area designation Establishing a trust Stopping the rot Legal Action Sources of further help and advice Links
Introduction
Manifesto Trustees Europe News Accounts
Privacy Policy
Introduction
This is the Privacy Policy of SAVE Britain’s Heritage (“SAVE”).  SAVE is a strong, independent voice in conservation that has been fighting for threatened historic buildings and sustainable reuses since 1975.
This Privacy Policy sets out the way we process your information and details. Personal data collected or provided by any means, whether it be completion of Support Us subscription forms, fundraising responses, emails, correspondence, social media, taking part in an event, event bookings or on-line purchases of publications or subscriptions and in the supply of goods or services are covered in the following Privacy Policy. This also includes information we receive from staff members, volunteers and job applicants.
For the purposes of the General Data Protection Regulation, the data controller in respect of your personal data is SAVE Britain’s Heritage a registered charity (no. 269129) whose address is 70, Cowcross Street, London, EC1M 6EJ.
How will we use personal information?
The personal information we collect might include your name, date of birth, address, email address and telephone number. If you make a donation online or purchase a product from us, your card information is not held by us, it is collected by our third-party payment processors, who specialise in the secure online capture and processing of credit/debit card transactions, as explained below.
Your personal data will have been collected by us in the ways stated in the introduction and will be used for the purposes outlined at the time of collection in accordance with the preferences you expressed.
We will use this data for the following purposes:
Administration of your subscription.
Fulfilment of orders for goods ordered form us via third parties - such as Gift Aid, World Pay, Charities Aid Foundation Bank, Amazon, PayPal and Eventbrite.
Administration of donations and legacies.
Research and statistical analysis including social media and subscriptions.
Communication about our campaigns, publications, events, subscriptions, fundraising and other activities that we think may be of interest to you by telephone, email and/or post (in accordance with your preferences).
If you subscribe to our email newsletter, we may notify you of information via post or email about our activities, events or products we think may be of interest to you, and how you can support us. SAVE will not share your details with anyone else without your consent or as required by law. In all cases where personal data is recorded, they will be stored securely.
If you do subscribe to our newsletter your name and email address are added to SAVE’s newsletter mailing list, which is managed via Mailchimp. Please note that Mailchimp may transfer personal data outside the EU. Please contact Mailchimp for more details about this.
Changing your preferences
We wish to ensure that you are completely happy with the personal data that we hold and how we use it. You can contact us at any time to check, update or amend your personal preferences. You can contact us by email at administrator@savebritainsheritage.org, by post to SAVE Britain’s Heritage, 70, Cowcross Street, London, EC1M 6EJ or by telephone on 020 7253 3500. These amendments will take place within 28 days of receipt of your request.
Retention
We will hold your information only as long as is necessary for us to administer your subscription or subscription to our e-newsletter. If your subscription lapses we may contact you for up to two years afterwards about rejoining.
Accessing your personal data held by SAVE Britain’s Heritage
All data subjects have the right:
To be informed about the collection and use of their personal data
To access personal data held about them
To rectification of the personal data
To erasure - be forgotten
To restrict processing, i.e. to request the restriction or suppression of their personal data
To data portability
To object
Rights in relation to automated decision making and profiling.
Should you wish to exercise any of these rights, please contact us in writing at the address below. If you request a copy of the personal data held about you, a copy will be sent to you as soon as possible but will not be later than 40 days after your request. If you are not happy with the way in which we have processed or dealt with your information, you can complain to the Information Commissioner’s Office. Further details about how to complain can be found here
SAVE Britain’s Heritage
70, Cowcross Street
London
EC1M 6EJ
or
administrator@savebritainsheritage.org
Links to third party websites
This Privacy Policy applies solely to the personal data collected by SAVE Britain’s Heritage and does not apply to third party websites and services that are not under our control.
Latest information
This Privacy Policy was written in May 2018 and contains the latest information regarding our privacy and fair processing notification. We will refer you to this page when we ask you for consent. This policy will be updated from time to time to reflect the latest view of what we do with your data.
LATEST TWEETS
Tweets by SAVEBrit
CONTACT SAVE
Contact SAVE
Support SAVE
Follow us on Instagram
Follow us on Twitter
Find us on Facebook
© 2020 SAVE Britain's Heritage | Registered Charity 269129 | Terms & Conditions
